So, welcome everybody, it's nice to see you all, today we offer at Camming Conf
idence
Call, which is going to be a bit of an overview really, a lot of things we talk
about all
the time, so everything to do with being confident on camp, making as much
money as possible,
and just how to get the best out of this career really, so it's a really good
call if you're
just starting out, or if you've been here a while and you just want to refresh
on the
latest stuff. I'm just going to mute everybody that's not muted. If you want to
ask a question
or chip in with anything at any time, just feel free to unmute yourself, put
your hand
up, and you can do. Okay, so let's get started. How beautiful does that girl
look? I'm not
on this, by the way, I love that picture so much. So, this is like one of my
favourite,
well, thank you Amy for meeting yourself, this is one of my favourite phrases,
and it's
one of my favourite people actually, so this lady, Maya Angelou, for those who
don't know,
she's, she was, she knocked around him up, she's like a poet, an author, a
civil rights
activist, a feminist, and one of her well-known phrases is that success is
liking yourself,
liking what you do and liking how you do it, and I just thought that was a
really good
way to summarise what we're going to talk about today because it's all about
being successful,
you know, having calm, calm confidence is about being successful, so it's
liking yourself,
the confidence in yourself, the confidence with what you're doing on cam and
how you're
doing it, and that's some of the stuff we're going to talk about today. Another
amazing
picture from the Thai shoot over the week. So, the components of calm success,
so we're
going to do one slide just on each of these components on how to get the best
out of your
calm-in and how to be successful on cam. So, these are the four components of,
you know,
being successful on cam, which are your profile, your skills, your confidence,
and your style,
so we're going to be in a bit more detail. So, skills, first of all. So, skill
is about
what you're actually doing, isn't it? It's about what you're actually doing and
saying
on cam, and I suppose it's the main thing that girls worry about, or they're
unsure
about when they first start, and because we're fed this image of what a calm
girl is supposed
to be, and we sort of see this like babe station girl, sort of like just
playing and, you know,
being provocative, like a porn star image, and a lot of girls think that that's
the skill
that that's what we're supposed to be doing, that that's the only thing we can
do, whereas
actually there's so much more to skill than just playing, and a lot of people
don't actually
play at all, so it's really good to sort of upskill yourself and think about
some of
these things. So, the first is persona and relationship building. So, we'll go
into a
bit more when we talk about, you know, your style, because that's a lot about
your style
is your persona and who you're going to be on cam, but it's really important
to sort
of develop your persona, so who you are on cam. So, what I say is, and sort of
what
I always think of when I'm thinking about the persona, is that it's about
showing who
you are, and not just what you can do. So, some people sort of profiles, if you
look
at them, it would just be like, I can do GFE, I can do this, I can play this, I
can do
that. But if you want to build a relationship with clients and get regulars who
are actually
invested in you, and you know, want to talk to you at length, and they're
interested
in you, and you're interested in them, if you want to build a relationship,
which is
all money, isn't it, then you need more than just a list of what you can do,
you need to
engage them and show them actually who you are. So, it might be who you
genuinely are,
or it might be a character, might be an alter ego that you've invented for your
canon,
but it's really important to have a little think about who's your persona, and
how can
you build relationships with your ideal clients. So, for instance, if you're a
dumb, if you're
thinking that you want to be more dominant, you might want to go and do a
domination course,
and then work on your persona, who you are, what's your backstory, how do you
relate to
your client, do you do a contract with them, what do they call you, what do you
call them,
and the same thing for any persona that you might have, so come up with a
little backstory,
know your character quite well, maybe even have a few little stories that you
can tell
about yourself, a few little sexy stories or whatever. We've got the fantasy
writing
course as well on the website, the call that you can watch to get some ideas.
So, have
a little bit about your, have a little think about your persona, and how you
can use that
persona to build relationships with clients, because that will get you people
coming back
and back, and that's a skill that's really useful with coming. Asking open
questions,
so when you're a bit stuck at first and you're not quite sure what to say, we
've got a list
of questions that your mentor sends you anyway, but they're all open questions.
So, thinking
about, is it the W words, isn't it that you ask for open questions, so like,
what, why,
who, where, asking questions that start with those words, so that the client
can elaborate,
so you're not just saying, do you like this, or whatever, you're asking
questions that
draw a bit more of a response out of them, so you can get to know them a bit
better,
drag the conversation on for a bit longer. So, open questions is a skill. Being
engaging,
so they say that, I can't remember what the percentage is, but it's such a
small percentage,
isn't it, of our communication is actually the words that we say. So, being
engaging
is all about your body language, you know, how much of you you can see on the
screen,
where you're facing, what you're doing, what if you're doing a little hair
flick, or if
you're like, adjusting yourself, or if you're, even if you're, what I tend to
do is leave
my microphone on, but I don't like to talk, so they can just hear a little g
iggle, or
if we're talking about something sexy, I'll give a big sigh, or just ways that
they can
show that I'm engaged with them and to get them to be engaged with me as well.
Knowing
your clients, so the same sort of thing with their relationship building, so
having a persona
and knowing what sort of clients like that persona. So, for example, we'll talk
about
this a bit more in the profile bit, because that's where you really want to
know your
client that you're marketing yourself to as well. But you want to have a little
thing,
over time, get to know, so this is not something that you'll know straight away
, over time,
get to notice what sort of guys are coming in your room, you know, what's their
age range,
what things do they respond well to, so you can try out different, saying
different little
stories or different movements even with your body, or different looks. Knowing
your client
is so important, because instead of trying to please every single person that
comes in
and trying to be the person that they want, because that's not possible for
every single
client, you want to be the best you that you can be for the clients that are
going to be
invested in you and going to stay with you the most time, you're going to keep
coming back.
So, notice what your high-paying clients are, notice the ones that are most
engaged,
and notice why, what do they respond well to, and what do they like when you
say or do,
what do they enjoy, and just keep a little note of them, so that you know your
clients and you
know what you like, so that you can do more of that. And the T's, so there are
many different
ways of course that you can tease, and we all have different styles and
different alter egos,
so if you ask any of us, it's probably different for all of us. For me, the T's
for me is in that
I'm a professional woman that is very capable and strong and intelligent, but I
'm also
highly sexual, and I could be dominant or submissive, it's like you bring it
out of me,
you just have to, you know, let's connect and find out what happens. So the T's
is that you
don't quite know what you're going to get other than, you know, a strong
intelligent woman that
maybe absolutely may not be. So the T's is all, for me, and the fantasy and the
relationship and
what's going to come out of it. For other people, the T's might be that your
brand news can,
you've never done anything like this before, you're experimenting with what you
might like,
you don't know anything about kink or whatever, so you want to find out a bit
more about that.
That's, you know, teasing guys with the possibility of what could happen and
what you could talk about.
So finding out how you can tease, how you can be provocative, without
necessarily going
a whole way, you know, straight away. What is it about your persona or about
what you're doing or
saying on camera is teasing and inviting more of a relationship or more of a
communication?
Is there anything anyone would add to those when it comes to skill?
And I know George would probably have lots to say, but I know you can't
George, because of the connection. But is there anything that anyone would add
to that skill bit,
do you think?
It's good to say as well that obviously that their welcome course on the
website will probably
go into much more detail than that when it comes to these sorts of things. And
so it's always good
to go through that as well. But yeah, there are a few pointers anyway, when it
comes to skill
and developing your skill on camera.
Okay, so next we have profile. So there are quite a few tips when it comes to
your profile.
So I just put these into three categories to try and make it easier.
So we've got setup. So your profile will be set up by admin.
But once you've been set up and come through to a mentor, you can still change,
you know,
whatever you want to change on there. So it's always good to think about the
basics of your
profile if they're working for you and your character and if you're getting the
most out of them.
So under the setup category. So under the setup category, you want to think
about your name.
So is your name really promoting who you want to be on cam? So, you know, for
instance, if you
want to talk about, if you want to be submissive, then you might want to make
sure that there's
sub in your name somewhere. If you want to be like the girl next door that's
quite innocent,
then you might just want to pick a more innocent name and not have any sort of
any extras in there. And yeah, just thinking about your name and what that
portrays about
your personality and whether that's going to appeal to the clients that you
want to appeal to.
So your location on your profile is important because that's where you're going
to come up in
the most searches. And also it helps with your confidence on cam. If you put
your location as
somewhere, you know, completely different to where you're actually coming from
so that you know that
you're not going to come up in any searches with anyone that's local to you
because that can be
something that can affect your cam confidence, can't it? If you're worried
about somebody,
you know, who's locals you find in your own cam. So location is really
important one to make sure
that you've got your location set with somewhere where you're happy with. And
then the bio. So of
course, the stuff we've already talked about. And when it comes to making the
most of your profile,
I've got profile template. So we've got, which some of you will know, we've got
a big profile
template, which we can send you, which goes through literally every single bit
of your profile,
how you should have it set, how you can alter it, you know, what are the best
things to do.
So to make the most out of your profile, we've got that profile template, which
also talks about
your bio, and how to get the most out of it, you know, what to put on there,
and loads of other
specific, you know, tips and tricks for your profiles. It's really worthwhile
looking at that
as your mentor for it. If you've not got it, or me or Georgia, we'll send it to
you. Maybe we can
just send it in the chat actually after this call anyway, but anyone else got
it.
And then promotion. So there are lots of different things that you can do to
try and promote
yourself. And again, on the welcome course, it goes through all of this. So it
also gives you
example profiles on the welcome course as well. So you can see what other
people's profiles look
like and try and model yours a bit. We'll take good bits from there. And so we
've got bidding.
Does anybody not know how to bid on their profile to make sure that they're on
the front page when
they come in? Does anybody not know that? Do you think I should go through it,
Georgia, just in
case? Do you think I should go through it? Or should we just, I might, I'll
have to probably come
out of this in order to do it. Or maybe we can just put a video in the chat
afterwards as well,
so we can put a few things in the chat that you can look back on. Yeah, maybe
that's the best way
to do it. So bidding. Yeah, Georgia says she'll send the video in the chat.
That's a good idea.
Okay. So you have the video there in chat and you'll understand how to bid to
ensure that you're
on the front page when you go online. So most skills will either bid so that
they're on the front
page or they'll do free chat or do a little bit of each. So if you go on free
chat, and we'll show
you again how to do that, your mental will let you know how to do that anyway,
how to put your
free chat on. And you can either go on to free chat, which means you're just in
a chat room,
lots of people are coming in and out and basically getting a little free view
of, you know, who you
are, and so that you can hook people into a group chat or a private chat from
there. Or if you don't
want to do that, you can bid to make sure that you're on the front page and
your profile is going
to be seen by more people when you're online. You can also link your Twitter to
your profile.
So that you can post on Twitter whenever you go online. You can, of course, put
a link on your
Instagram. You do have to be careful with Instagram, obviously what you share
because their guidelines
are a lot more strict. But you can put a link on your Instagram or just say
that you're on
AdultWork now, you know, message me for the link or whatever, another way for
most things.
Content, so it's always good to think about what content you're putting on
there. So, you know,
the quality of your pictures, what you're wearing, the settings, you're having
a range of different
photos and having enough content. I personally try and put a picture on my
profile every week or
when, you know, when you want to know I'm going to be on for a few days, I'll
put one or two pictures
on because it just boosts your profile and gets you seen a bit more. I think
the people that are
on your hot list as well get to see when you put new pictures up through their
Georgia. Or they
always comment anyway when I put something new up, they immediately message me
and say that they
love my new pictures. So it's a good way to stay in the minds of your regulars
as well.
Feedback, so feedback is a good way to promote yourself and to market yourself.
So whenever you've
had calls with people, make sure that you give them feedback and try to get
feedback from them as well.
So if you've been coming and you've had chats with people, then you click,
log into your profile and click on your messages on the message tab. It will
say you've got outstanding
feedback for blah, blah, blah. So there you can give them great feedback, you
know, ask the feedback,
ask them to give you some and save it and yeah, just get some thinking about
you and the more
feedback you've got on the profile, the better. And then special offers, that's
another way to
promote yourself. It's not something that I've done for a long time. So it's
not something I'm
overly familiar with, but if you go onto your webcam settings, it's from there,
isn't it? You can,
you can put special offers on. So when you're editing your profile, you can
just put offers,
you can put a certain amount for a certain amount of time or whatever to get
people coming in.
Okay, so that's a profile.
So next we've got confidence. So this is thinking about your personal
confidence, which when we say
about having confidence, probably where a lot of people's minds go to, isn't it
? Because a lot of
people, like either completely miss out on this opportunity, you know, the
incredible opportunity
that coming can be, or don't reach their full potential because it's their
actual self-confidence
that's holding them back, which is, you know, really sad to see because we all
have the potential
to do so well on cam. And just a few things, a few pointers here, and I think
Sophie's going
to talk a bit more about this at the end, about body confidence specifically.
But just a few
pointers here, so the mainstream beauty lie. So what I mean by that is that we
have to be aware
that as women, particularly our conditioning and the view we have of ourselves
is heavily
influenced by society, by a patriarchal society, by capitalism, by, you know,
men in boardrooms
trying to sell us things, which means they have to make us feel bad about
ourselves so that we buy
their products. And the whole world of society is set up on this system, and it
's so quiet and so
normal, so every day that we don't question it, we just see all these adverts
or these magazines,
these insta posts, whatever, and we just feel bad about ourselves. So first of
all, we need to
acknowledge for our own confidence, whether it's coming or just in general,
that this is a lie,
that this is based on money and oppression, and that actually there are a
variety of men out there,
and it's not even about gender, but there are a variety of people out there who
find different
things attractive, and that it's not just this really slim idea of what is
attractive that is
actually attractive. So how well a girl does on cam has nothing to do with her
clothes size or
bra size or age or any of those things, and it's literally about how much
conditioning can you
throw off, how much how much do you can you be, and how much can you enjoy
yourself and your time,
because I think that just comes across so much, and it enables other people
then to, you know,
your clients to bask in your energy and enjoy you as much as you're enjoying
you, and also enjoy
themselves. It gives them a pass to be themselves and not have to live up to
some, you know, unrealistic
ideal as well. So yeah, acknowledging that there is this mainstream beauty lie,
and it doesn't
apply to us when we're on cam, you know, the more comfortable with yourself you
can be the better,
because a lot of the time then things that you're thinking in your head is only
you thinking it,
the other people that are in your chat room are already there paying to see you
, so they're not,
they're not thinking those things. Take inspiration from other people, so, you
know,
yeah, in life or we're coming as well. I still do this, so I just go online and
flick through
some profiles and I think, oh, that looks good, or I'll see a photo that I like
, and then I'll recreate
it next time I go to one of our shoots, or, yeah, just take inspiration from
the women that are
around you, you know, women in the group even, you know, our members' postings
that they're doing,
or whatever sometimes, and I think, oh, it's a great idea. It's like some of
the girls will go
online with like an ice lollie in the summer to keep cool, but it also looks
sexy, and I'm like,
oh yeah, great, I'll take inspiration from them, I'll do that. And so always
taking inspiration
from the people around you, and this goes for online as well, so, like my
Instagram feed,
if there's anything that makes me feel bad about myself, it's just instantly
cut from it,
because I don't want that energy, and I don't want to be beating myself up
about anything, so,
I really make a point of following people that make me feel inspired, that make
me feel amazing,
and because that's conditioning you as well, you know, so that's really
important.
Treating yourself with care, so it might seem obvious, or even hard for a lot
of people, but
I think there's a lot of good tips and things that we talked about in
what was its self-worth, insects work, all that we did, so you can go back on
the members area and
watch that call. There's loads of things that, and those are tips that we gave
on how we treat
ourselves with care, how we, you know, work on our own self-worth, and love
ourselves, essentially,
because that's what it is. Yeah, a couple of people have commented on, to me,
you know, privately,
or more than a couple, that they've taken things from that call, and that they
've done, you know,
implemented them, and it's helped them to feel a lot better, so that's lovely,
that might be a
call we're watching back. Finding what feels good for you, so when it comes to
calm, yeah,
finding what feels good for you, I mean, there's no point squeezing into a
little outfit that
makes you feel like shit, and then trying to do what you think you should be
doing,
where, what feels good on you, where, what you feel sexy in, you know, do what
you feel sexy doing,
think about where you are, you know, maybe you want to be on the sofa, maybe
you want to be in bed,
or on your desk, you know, just do what feels good for you, instead of just
sort of facing
everything on what you think your client wants, start from what you want, and
when you feel good,
and when you feel sexy, you are sexy, you know, so find what feels good for you
in all the ways
and do that, and then routine and habit, so again, that's kind of similar to
treating
yourself with care, because part of treating yourself with care is having good
routine rituals
and good habits, and so like putting your favourite playlist on before you go on
calm,
and then Georgia likes to like put nice body lotion on and just rub that in all
over before
you go on cam, and a little, little habits like having a little thing on your
mirror, just just a
little motivational quote or something that you look at when you're getting
ready before you go on,
say things that get you into the right headspace, and so that you're feeling
good already when
you go online, and that's better for you already, and okay,
and then we have style, so style is such a big part of whether or not you're a
successful on
calm, or whether or not you enjoy it as well, I think, because there's so many
other agencies
that don't talk about this, or they just, some of the main ones even just do
kind of a template,
and everyone's profile looks the same, everyone is like big juicy tits, big ass
, blah blah blah,
and there's no thought for style, or individuality, or uniqueness, or like play
fulness, or creativity,
all that stuff, which feels so good, which you can be playful with, and it's a
good way to experiment
with what keep clients alike from you, and what you enjoy doing, so that you
can hone down on your
niche a little bit more, and find out what you enjoy to do, so here are some of
the different
niches, and there's loads, or some of the different things to think about when
you're thinking about
your niche, so some of the different categories or niches that you might think
about are of course
DOM, which we have a course on on the website, submissive, which we will have a
course on,
it is written, and we'll be up soon, we'll just go do some finishing touches,
so that's one
category to think about, and you can obviously Google these things, and there's
so much information
online about what you can do, and the girlfriend experience, so GFE, Taboo,
ones that are based
around your job role, so you know, you're a nurse, or how do we always think
for nurse, that's always
the one thing you come, because that's what I used to say I do, but you can
base your niche around
whatever your made up job is, or any of the fetishes, so like, foot fetish,
second skin, you know, latex,
stuff like that, there's so many different niches that you can try out, and
when you're thinking
about what you're trying, and what niche you're trying, these are the
considerations that you
can look at, so clothing, does what you're wearing on can reflect, you know,
the thing that you're
trying to play with, or get across, the setting and the lighting, so yeah, does
the lighting
reflect your personality and your niche, and your experience, so what
experience have you got,
like how much of yourself can you bring into your character, because it's all
relevant, and it all
helps, and your relationship to your client, so of course, your relationship to
your client is
going to be very different if you're a dom, or if you're a sub, and so the way
that you speak to them,
the language you use with them, even where the camera is placed, so if you're a
dom, for instance,
you might want to have like the camera more down, basically awkward, so you're
looking down on it,
but if you're more sub, you might want to have it more like this, so that you
're just, you know,
you're more equal in how you come in across on cam, and of course, your profile
, so your profile
wants to reflect the kind of things that you do in the person you are on cam,
so it might not be
that you stick to one niche, it might not really stick to one specific thing,
but it's good if you,
it really comes across who you are, what you like to experiment with on your
profile, so that you
can get a good sense of who they're going to be coming with. Okay, that's it
for my incessant
talking, I do have a couple more things, because I thought we could go to any
of our mentors,
our founders that want to talk and just give some of their own personal tips,
but I think I
will hand over to someone else, so Sammy or Sophie, do either of you want to
have a little,
do you either of you want to chip in here, so what your sort of tips are, any
tips you would give for
cam confidence? Yeah I've got my bit on body confidence, do you want me to do
that in a bit?
Yes please, yeah please. Okay, can you still hear me if I do that?
Yeah, I've got a few notes written on my phone, I do love to write notes.
Okay, so I think I'm quite lucky in that I've got a lot of body confidence,
self confidence,
but for me that is learned behaviour, I literally faked it until I made it,
I was like typical geeky kid, curly ginger hair, pale skin, freckles, anxious,
so I was easy to
pick on, babies looking at me now, like why are you talking?
Yeah, get back from the beer if I'm busy now.
So, and I was just very, very insecure as a child and as a teenager, sort of
semi-anorexic,
when I was a teenager, hated my body, hated my weight, and yeah, so when I was
clearly more
attractive to people, or you know, you start getting chatted up and whatever,
and I was just like,
what the hell is going on? And I suffer with depression and anxiety anyway,
that never helps
with anything, and then I just sort of started faking it until I made it, and
just pretending
I was the best person in the world, and then eventually it started feeling like
I was pretending,
because there's only one me, there's only one of each of us, there's only, you
know, we've got
individual unique bodies, styles, personalities, everything, so you need to
absolutely own yourself,
don't say, oh I'm going to be happy when I lose a stone, I'm going to be happy
when I'm a size 12,
I'm going to be happy when my hair does this, I'm going to be happy when I wear
this certain makeup,
it doesn't work like that, you need to be so happy and confident in your own
skin,
like I feel like a state today, I didn't have time to get ready, I'm literally,
it's probably a bit ironic really, I literally wanted to put something nice on
and put makeup on
to talk about body confidence, but it's probably better that I've got my hair
thrown or no makeup,
baby hanging off my teeth, I just, you know, I feel great, my anxiety and I'm a
bit, mental health is
a bit, but I feel great because I am great and everything's great, and that's
what everybody
needs to think about themselves, get on cam and say there's only one me, you've
got an initial,
you know, there will be an initial attraction to you, they would have seen your
photos,
so you know like Ralph said, take great photos, feel great in those photos,
there will be an
attraction to you, so then that's why they're coming into your room and then
just own yourself,
give a nice big smile straight into the camera, like I'm looking at the camera
right now so you
guys can see my eyes on the screen, that's what the client would say, so it
feels like I contact
them, you can like back your eyelashes and be like oh hey, and I genuinely
smile when I think
they're paying me right now, I'm sitting here doing hard, they're paying and
then
that's what makes me smile, you know, you might just think of something that
makes you smile and
the client will think it's them, that's fine, my notes are kind of scroll, so
yeah there's no such
thing as perfection, you are the perfect you, there's no other you, so yeah if
you had a perfect
body, you know, whatever that may be, if you look at someone else and think oh
they're perfect,
I'm not that, but they might have no confidence, I've met so many attractive
people and they go,
yeah but now I'm not, I'm not attractive, but attraction is in the eye of the
beholder,
if they're coming to you, they find you attractive and just own that, look at
yourself like you are
the most beautiful person in the world, because you are, we're all stunning and
the world would
be boring if we were all the same, like Ralph said all the girls with similar
photos, similar body
types, like the same profiles, that's no fun, that you know it's about variety,
so they'll go and
look at everyone and then find what they like and if you're what they like,
perfect, so you're
not selling your body, you are renting out your time, so if they want to spend
time with you, they
have to pay and that's, you know, that's how we make money off this, your time
is extremely
valuable, time is literally money, so the longer you can keep them in your room
, the better.
Thank you, I can't fruit, I brought to me, um, was I, so yeah you want to show
off your best
asset, which is your personality and your brain and your skills, what Ralph
discussed earlier,
um, so since coming for four years I've realised that men are very simple
creatures,
and I mean I don't want to be disrespectful, I love men, I love women, I love
people, but they,
men do seem people wide differently to women, you find like, you know, we
always talk about society
and, um, they, the pressure on women and I think that comes from men initially,
we're going to think women stick to wearing certain makeup and clothes and
doing certain
things for all the women, it's usually women that say, oh that's a nice dress,
oh I love your
Oh Sophie, you've muted yourself, um, men tend to do that, they go with makeup,
they'll go,
wow you're naturally pretty, wow your body's nice, they can see under the
clothes and under the
makeup, um, I feel like if I wear too much makeup, I just look awful, um, like
the little child being
in a mum's makeup box, um, so yeah I find the less clothes, the less makeup I
wear, the more attractive
I seem to be, because I have to really, you know, push myself a concert, um,
when you, when you're
hoping for a kind of vibe, I will, you know, oh hi, hi, I'm like, oh you've got
big beautiful
blue eyes, I'm like, yeah, yeah, because I'll always have a light source behind
my eyes and just,
you know, accentuate your, what you feel like is your best features and you'll
probably
learn what most men find as your best features because they might comment on it
,
then just work, work to that, um, if I'm putting makeup on during calm, the
guys will just go,
I'm like, oh just let me just finish on the like whatever, I'll come back, um,
yeah obviously they
don't care, like I've had the camera away before, I've gone, I'm just doing
makeup, I'm like, I don't
care, come in now and I'm like, oh okay, and this day, because they want me,
not me with makeup, um,
most of you know I regularly go on from the bath, so I literally get up and put
my contact lenses in,
maybe throw on a bit of mascara, I hate my, I hate my ashes, so I'll put a bit
of mascara on and
jump in the bath, um, and, or I'll wake up first thing in the morning, usually
put contact lenses
in, I don't like wearing my glasses on camp, that's, that's a thing with me,
but I should not care,
because guys go, oh I like the glasses, you know it's quirky and yeah, um, just
said that said that,
so yeah I said before about faking it, um, so I'll go on, I'm not feeling 100%,
but I'll get a
boost off the clients being lovely, um commenting on, you know, how attractive
I am and whatever,
um, and if you've, if I'm really really not feeling it, then I just won't go on
, I'll,
you know, have some self-care instead, and that works wonders for me, um, or
you could, you know,
do a nice, um, treatment on yourself, a face mask, hair mask, you know, just
have a nice bath, um,
or you could just work on your profile, you know, try and get in the mood,
stick some photos,
um, but I always try and keep my profile updated, so, um, so it's always fresh,
you know, and I always
put in my profile summary, I'm just doing this, I'm just in the bath, or I'm
just out and about,
and just keeps it updated and fresh and fun, and just have fun, if you're not
having fun,
that will show through and just, you know, own yourself, I can't stress enough,
own yourself,
say, oh, I hate my boobs, you know, put a, put a nice bra on and get them out
on cam, and you'll
soon realise you have beautiful boobs, you don't like your legs, you know, just
moisturize them,
shave them, do whatever you want, I've gone on with, I go on cam with hairy
legs, hairy bits,
everything, I just don't care, so just don't care, be like a man, wake up in
the morning,
barely wash yourself, and then go to work, because maybe that's why they, um,
they don't care,
because a lot of men don't have a good self care routine, but, you know, do
what makes you feel
the best, and your confidence will shine through, and that's it, I think, I
wrote a little essay,
sorry to try to get through that really quickly, but, um, if anyone's got any
questions about that,
probably you're looking at me like, I'll go bitch, where should you get a
confidence plan, but I don't
care, I'll do that, don't finish it off with that, say no, no, but you know
what I mean, you've,
there's always that voice in your head going, you're not that great, you're not
that great,
but I am, and you all are, everybody has their own unique, amazing qualities,
and amazing features
physically and mentally and emotionally, and just work on that, this is all I
can say,
thank you. Thank you so much, thank you so much, honestly that was so good, um,
and yet it was
inspiring me so much, so much of what you said, um, so important, all of it isn
't it, um, yeah,
you too, what you do with what you were saying as well, it's great. Yeah, and
this is part of what
this is about as well, like, you know, in any of our calls or whatever, we've
all, all of us have
got something to offer, it's not like this, like us and them mentality, it's
like we're all together
in this, um, and that's what I was thinking as well, that we hadn't mentioned
like just talking,
like using this community, that's the beauty of this community, is that you're
feeling insecure,
or you're not sure about something, or you think you've done something wrong,
or whatever it is,
there's so many women out there that have one probably done it, and two are
just
willing to support you at the drop of a hat, that's what's amazing about this
group, so,
but yeah, that's a big part of cam confidence, isn't it, that you can ask any
question at any
time, and it's never going to be judged, or whatever, you know, we're all in
the same boat.
Yeah, um, one thing I was just thinking why you was, why you're talking is
about flickers as well,
we haven't mentioned that, that's a big thing, isn't it, for cam confidence, it
's something that
can knock your confidence at the start, is when people are coming into your
room and then leaving
straight away, so yeah, it's a good time to mention that that happens all the
time to every one of
those, it doesn't matter how successful you are, how long you've been on with
all them flickers,
it happens every time, it's not about trying to get every flicker to stay,
because they're not,
they're just picking through, you know, half them probably don't have credits,
they're just looking
for something for nothing basically, so don't take that as any reflection on
you, or you're with,
or you're a beauty, or anything, because it's nothing to do with you, it's just
a habit that
they've got, or whatever, you know, there's loads of different reasons it might
be.
Yeah, um, Cali's just said what our flickers, it's like clients that just come
in and out,
they'll come in, stay for three seconds and leave, and if it can knock your
confidence,
you're like, oh my god, they don't like me, and so what if they don't like you,
that just leaves
room for the guys that are gonna like you, they'll flick through, find you,
love ya, or like Ralph
said, they're just, they've got no credits, and they're hoping to get a flash
of boob or something,
and just, yeah, be pathetic like that. Yeah, yeah, and what you were saying
about your,
like the reaction to clients, you, it was making me think about the reactions
clients, like,
and to acknowledge that it's an acting job basically, like, like being happy,
smiling,
giving them a reaction, you know, making them feel like they're the only one, I
mean, I will
literally say that to guys on ham, you're the only one, you're the one that
makes me feel like
I can be myself, like, oh, I never do this, I've never done this on ham before,
but you made me
feel so comfortable, I mean, if I had a pound for every time I said that, it's
gonna be a millionaire,
so just, you know, you're my boyfriend, oh, I'm so happy you're back, oh, I don
't do this with
anybody else, oh, I, you're just fast. Yeah, yeah, even to the point where a
lot of my clients
think I'm only a Dom, they think I'm only a Dom, but then I only am submissive
to that one person,
or I only ever have done this for you, but of course that's not the truth, but
they feel special,
or it makes them come back back. There's some other things in the chat, so I
had a direct message
from somebody asking about changing their location, so you can change a
location on the edit profile
bit, but unfortunately, you can't change the country, you can only change the
location within the country,
so yeah, the country that you're verified to, unfortunately, we can't change
that, we can
only change wherever you are in the country, so the region, or whatever, and
your mentor can show
you how to do that. And then we've got Georgia, so I love watching this, thanks
Alan South,
Georgia tips are to remember to do what feels good, remember you've got the
power, you're in
control, so enjoy it, of course, yeah, we haven't mentioned that, you can
finish the call at any
time, or block someone or whatever, so you're always in control, and relax,
connect with the client,
and connect with yourself, what are your desires? Yeah, we haven't really
talked about that, have we,
how it's about your own pleasure as well at the end of the day, I mean, you may
be purely acting,
or you may actually enjoy some of the stuff you're talking about or doing, I
know I do, so I think
thinking about what I like is important to me, have fun and watch the money add
up,
and then Sammy, Sammy's best bit of advice would be to be playful and have fun
with it,
even if it's being a bit silly, especially when you're starting out, don't
worry about getting
anything wrong, or trying different styles on personas until you find your
niche, yeah, that's
another thing we haven't really said, that you can change your profile at any
time, and it changes
with you on your journey, so you don't have to stick to being one thing, you
can be one thing,
then another, then another, you know, it can change with you. If you're having
fun and enjoying
yourself while working, it will shine through on cam, and consistency will help
with the nerves,
and yeah, that's really good point, that consistency helps, the avoidance is
the friend of anxiety,
so if whatever you're avoiding grows your anxiety around that thing, so just do
it, just get on,
if you're really feeling, you know, really anxious or whatever, just message
your mental,
message in the group, get yourself into a good space, and just log on, because
whatever's happening
in your head, I can guarantee you, is 10 times worse than what's actually going
to happen when
you log on, just stop talking to you, and that last little thing, because I
think it's mostly
been said, is, well, a couple of things, personally, don't feel you have to
abandon yourself in order
to be what the client wants, I mean, I say this, this is so important in life
anyway, don't abandon
yourself from what I mean by that is your own need, your own desires, your own
personality,
anything that's for you, you don't need to abandon any of that stuff in order
to make it on cam,
inhabit that stuff, like use that stuff, that's your power, like, so instead of
abandoning any
thoughts or feelings or whatever's coming up, use it, use it to your advantage,
because you,
like Sophie says, are the only one of you, that is your power. And the final
thing,
we also did a manifestation call, a little while back, which might be a good
one to watch as well,
because it's really good to sort of use manifestation hacks to help you in your
journey,
goal setting, and setting your intentions, and manifesting your ideal clients.
So this is what
I try and do, and it always seems to work really, is that I manifest the client
that I want. So,
I always think of these three things when it comes to manifestation, intention,
attention,
and action. So my intention is that, for instance, recently, I was like, I want
a couple of sub clients,
I want more sub clients, I want to do more jobbing. Okay, I'm going to have it,
I'm going to go online
and I'm going to have the client that is going to just be like this. And I
thought about them in my
head, I thought I imagined how it was going to go, how it was going to feel,
put myself in that space,
believed it, believed that it was coming. So that was my intention is setting
the belief and believing
it's coming. And then my attention, I paid attention by editing my profile a
little bit,
thinking about what I was wearing, making sure I was going on at a time that
seems to me.
So it was in my attention, I kept that intention with me while I was on cam,
and then action. So I talked more about wanting to be dumb, I sort of took
action that was in line
with my manifestation. So intention, attention, and action, whatever you want
to get, whatever client
you want to manifest, those three things stick with them, and it will happen.
Okay, anybody else want to add anything before we finish up? I think that
brings us quite nicely,
we've just got five minutes left before one o'clock. Does anyone want to ask a
question or add anything?
I'm trying to go through and look at everybody.
Oh, we all good. I see a little baby feet on Sophie's screen, so cute.
Okay, ladies, well, thank you so much for coming. Like we always say, if anyone
's got any questions
that they didn't want to ask here, then just speak to your mentor or message
one of us or message
in the group. This recording will be up on the website today or tomorrow, so
you can watch it
back if there's any bits you missed or whatever. Thank you ladies, thank you
for coming. And next
call is next Thursday, and it's with after toggle for call. So that's all about
posing and content
and getting good photos ahead of our shoots in a couple of weeks. So we'll see
you next Thursday,
hopefully. Thank you ladies. Thank you, thanks everyone for listening. Bye.